<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    //------------------------------BARBARIAN---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string-array name="barbarianAbilityList">
        <item>Barbarian Abilities</item>
        <item>Rage</item>
        <item>Unarmored Defense</item>
        <item>Reckless Attack</item>
        <item>Danger Sense</item>
        <item>Feral Instinct</item>
        <item>Brutal Critical</item>
        <item>Relentless Rage</item>
        <item>Persistent Rage</item>
        <item>Indomitable Might</item>
        <item>Primal Champion</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="barbarianAbilityDescription">
        <item>Barbarian Ability Description</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            In battle, you fight with primal ferocity. On your turn,
            you can enter a rage as a <b>bonus action</b>.
            While raging, you gain the following benefits if you
            aren’t wearing heavy armor:
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>
            • You have advantage on Strength checks and Strength
            saving throws.
            <br>
            <br>
            • When you make a melee weapon attack using
            Strength, you gain a bonus to the damage roll that
            increases as you gain levels as a barbarian, as shown
            in the Rage Damage column of the Barbarian table.
            <br>
            <br>
            • You have resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and
            slashing damage.
            </b>
            <br>
            <br>
            If you are able to cast spells, you can’t cast them or
            concentrate on them while raging.
            <br>
            <br>
            Your rage <b>lasts for 1 minute</b>. It ends early if you are
            knocked unconscious or if your turn ends and you
            haven’t attacked a hostile creature since your last turn
            or taken damage since then. You can also end your rage
            on your turn as a bonus action.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you have raged the number of times shown
            for your barbarian level in the Rages column of the
            Barbarian table, you must finish a long rest before you
            can rage again.

            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            While you are not wearing any armor, your Armor Class
            equals <b>10 + your Dexterity modifier + your Constitution
            modifier</b>.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can use a shield and still gain this benefit.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can throw aside all concern
            for defense to attack with fierce desperation.
            <br>
            <br>
            When you make your first attack on your turn, you can decide
            to attack recklessly. Doing so gives you <b>advantage on
            melee weapon attack rolls using Strength during this
            turn</b>, but attack rolls against you have advantage until
            your next turn.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>2nd level</b>, you gain an uncanny sense of when things
            nearby aren’t as they should be, giving you an edge
            when you dodge away from danger.
            <br>
            <br>
            You have <b>advantage on Dexterity saving throws
            against effects that you can see</b>, such as traps and spells.
            To gain this benefit, you can’t be blinded, deafened, or
            incapacitated.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            By <b>7th level</b>, your instincts are so honed that you have
            </b>advantage on initiative rolls.</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            Additionally, if you are surprised at the beginning of
            combat and aren’t incapacitated, you can act normally
            on your first turn, but only if you enter your rage before
            doing anything else on that turn.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>9th level</b>, you can roll one additional
            weapon damage die when determining the extra
            damage for a critical hit with a melee attack.
            <br>
            <br>
            This increases to two additional dice at 13th level
            and three additional dice at 17th level.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>11th level</b>, your rage can keep you fighting
            despite grievous wounds. If you drop to 0 hit points
            while you’re raging and don’t die outright, you can make
            a <b>DC 10 Constitution saving throw.</b> If you succeed , you
            drop to <b>1 hit point</b> instead.
            <br>
            <br>
            Each time you use this feature after the first, the DC
            in creases by 5. When you finish a short or long rest, the
            DC resets to 10.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>15th level</b>, your rage is so fierce that
            it ends early only if you fall unconscious or if you
            choose to end it.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>18th level</b>, if your total for a Strength
            check is less than your Strength score, you can use that
            score in place of the total.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>20th level</b>, you embody the power of the wilds. Your
            Strength and Constitution scores increase by 4. Your
            maximum for those scores is now 24.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="barbarianPrimalPathTitle">
        Primal Paths
    </string>

    <string name="barbarianPrimalPath">
        <![CDATA[
        Rage burns in every barbarian’s heart, a furnace
        that drives him or her toward greatness. Different
        barbarians attribute their rage to different sources,
        however. For some, it is an internal reservoir where
        pain, grief, and anger are forged into a fury hard as
        steel. Others see it as a spiritual blessing, a gift of
        a totem animal.
        <br>
        <br>
        At <b>3rd level</b>, you choose a path that shapes the nature of
        your rage. Choose the Path of the Berserker or the Path
        of the Totem Warrior. Your choice grants you features at 3rd
        level and again at <b>6th, 10th, and 14th levels.</b>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="barbarianPathOfBerserker">
        <item>Path of the Berserker</item>
        <item>Frenzy</item>
        <item>Mindless Rage</item>
        <item>Intimidating Presence</item>
        <item>Retaliation</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="barbarianPathOfBerserkerDescription">
        <item>Path of the Berserker Abilities Descriptions</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting when you choose this path at <b>3rd level</b>, you
            can go into a frenzy when you rage. If you do so, for
            the duration of your rage you can make a single melee
            weapon attack as a bonus action on each of your turns
            after this one. When your rage ends, you suffer one level
            of exhaustion.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>6th level</b>, you can’t be charmed or
            frightened while raging. If you are charmed or
            frightened when you enter your rage, the effect is
            suspended for the duration of the rage.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>10th level</b>, you can use your action to
            frighten someone with your menacing presence.
            When you do so, choose one creature that you can see
            within 30 feet of you.
            <br>
            If the creature can see or hear
            you, it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw <b>(DC
            equal to 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma
            modifier)</b> or be frightened of you until the end of your
            next turn.
            <br>
            <br>
            On subsequent turns, you can use your action
            to extend the duration of this effect on the frightened
            creature until the end of your next turn. This effect ends
            if the creature ends its turn out of line of sight or more
            than 60 feet away from you.
            <br>
            <br>
            If the creature succeeds on its saving throw, you can\'t
            use this feature on that creature again for 24 hours.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>14th level</b>, when you take damage from
            a creature that is within 5 feet of you. you can use
            your reaction to make a melee weapon attack against
            that creature.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="barbarianPathOfTotemWarrior">
        <item>Path of the Totem Warrior</item>
        <item>Spirit Seeker</item>
        <item>Totem Spirit</item>
        <item>Aspect of the Beast</item>
        <item>Spirit Walker</item>
        <item>Totemic Attunement</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="barbarianPathOfTotemWarriorDescription">
        <item>Path of the Totem Warrior</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Yours is a path that seeks attunement with the natural
            world, giving you a kinship with beasts. At <b>3rd level</b> when
            you adopt this path, you gain the ability to cast the <b>beast
            sense</b> and <b>speak with animals</b> spells, but only as rituals,
            as described in chapter 10.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>3rd level</b>, when you adopt this path, you choose a
            totem spirit and gain its feature. You must make or
            acquire a physical totem object - an amulet or similar
            adornment — that in corporates fur or feathers, claws,
            teeth, or bones of the totem animal. At your option, you
            also gain minor physical attributes that are reminiscent
            of your totem spirit. For example, if you have a bear
            totem spirit, you might be unusually hairy and thick-
            skinned, or if your totem is the eagle, your eyes turn
            bright yellow.
            <br>
            <br>
            Your totem animal might be an animal related to those
            listed here but more appropriate to your homeland.
            <br>
            For exam ple, you could choose a hawk or vulture in
            place of an eagle.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Bear:</b> While raging, you have resistance to all damage
            except psychic damage. The spirit of the bear makes you
            tough enough to stand up to any punishment.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Eagle:</b> While you’re raging and aren’t wearing
            heavy armor, other creatures have disadvantage on
            opportunity attack rolls against you, and you can use the
            Dash action as a bonus action on your turn. The spirit
            of the eagle makes you into a predator who can weave
            through the fray with ease.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Wolf:</b> While you’re raging, your friends have
            advantage on melee attack rolls against any creature
            within 5 feet of you that is hostile to you. The spirit of
            the wolf makes you a leader of hunters.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, you gain a magical benefit based on the
            totem animal of your choice. You can choose the same
            animal you selected at 3rd level or a different one.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Bear:</b> You gain the might of a bear. Your carrying
            capacity (including maximum load and maximum lift)
            is doubled, and you have advantage on Strength checks
            made to push, pull, lift, or break objects.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Eagle:</b> You gain the eyesight of an eagle. You can
            see up to 1 mile away with no difficulty, able to discern
            even fine details as though looking at something no
            more than 100 feet away from you. Additionally, dim
            light doesn\'t impose disadvantage on your Wisdom
            (Perception) checks.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Wolf:</b> You gain the hunting sensibilities of a wolf. You
            can track other creatures while traveling at a fast pace,
            and you can move stealthily while traveling at a normal
            pace (see chapter 8 for rules on travel pace).
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>10th level</b>, you can cast the commune with nature
            spell, but only as a ritual. When you do so, a spiritual
            version of one of the animals you chose for Totem Spirit
            or Aspect of the Beast appears to you to convey the
            information you seek.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>14th level</b>, you gain a magical benefit based on a
            totem animal of your choice. You can choose the same
            animal you selected previously or a different one.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Bear:</b> While you’re raging, any creature within 5 feet
            of you that’s hostile to you has disadvantage on attack
            rolls against targets other than you or another character
            with this feature. An enemy is immune to this effect if it
            can’t see or hear you or if it can’t be frightened.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Eagle:</b> While raging, you have a flying speed equal to
            your current walking speed. This benefit work s only in
            short bursts; you fall if you end your turn in the air and
            nothing else is holding you aloft.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Wolf:</b> While you\'re raging, you can use a bonus action
            on your turn to knock a Large or smaller creature prone
            when you hit it with melee weapon attack.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //------------------------------BARD---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string-array name="bardAbilityList">
        <item>Bard Abilities</item>
        <item>Bardic Inspiration</item>
        <item>Jack of all Trades</item>
        <item>Song of Rest</item>
        <item>Expertise</item>
        <item>Font of Inspiration</item>
        <item>Countercharm</item>
        <item>Magical Secrets</item>
        <item>Superior Inspiration</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bardAbilityDescriptions">
        <item>Bard Abilities Descriptions</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            You can inspire others through stirring words or music.
            To do so, you use a <b>bonus action</b> on your turn to choose
            one creature other than yourself <b>within 60 feet of you
            who can hear you.</b> That creature gains one Bardic
            Inspiration die, a <b>d6</b>.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll
            the die and add the number rolled to one <b>ability check,
            attack roll, or saving throw</b> it makes. The creature can
            wait until after it rolls the d20 before deciding to use the
            Bardic Inspiration die, but must decide before the DM
            says whether the roll succeeds or fails. Once the Bardic
            Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have
            only on e Bardic Inspiration die at a time.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can use this feature a number of times equal
            to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You
            regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach
            certain levels in this class. <b>The die becomes a d8 at 5th
            level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can add half your proficiency
            bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that
            doesn’t already include your proficiency bonus.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use soothing music or
            oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during
            a short rest. If you or any friendly creatures who can
            hear your performance regain hit points at the end of
            the short rest, each of those creatures regains an extra
            </b>1d6 hit points.</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>The extra hit points increase when you reach certain
            levels in this class: to 1d8 at 9th level, to 1d10 at 13th
            level, and to 1d12 at 17th level.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>3rd level</b>, choose two of your skill proficiencies. Your
            proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you
            make that uses either of the chosen proficiencies.
            <br>
            <br>
            At 10th level, you can choose another two skill
            proficiencies to gain this benefit.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning when you reach <b>5th level</b>, you regain all of
            your expended uses of Bardic Inspiration w hen you
            finish a short or long rest.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, you gain the ability to use musical notes or
            words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. As
            an <b>action</b>, you can start a performance that lasts until
            the end of your next turn. During that time, you and any
            friendly creatures within 30 feet of you have <b>advantage
            on saving throws against being frightened or charmed.</b>
            <br>
            A creature must be able to hear you to gain this benefit.
            The performance ends early if you are incapacitated or
            silenced or if you voluntarily end it (no action required).
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            By <b>10th level</b>, you have plundered magical knowledge
            from a wide spectrum of disciplines. Choose two spells
            from any class, including this one. A spell you choose
            must be of a level you can cast, as shown on the Bard
            table, or a cantrip.
            <br>
            <br>
            The chosen spells count as bard spells for you and are
            included in the number in the Spells Known column of
            the Bard table.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>You learn two additional spells from any class at 14th
            level and again at 18th level.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>20th level</b>, when you roll initiative and have no uses
            of Bardic Inspiration left, you regain one use.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="bardCollegeTitle">
        Bard College
    </string>

    <string name="bardCollegeDescription">
        <![CDATA[
        The way of a bard is gregarious. Bards seek each
        other out to swap songs and stories, boast of their
        accomplishments, and share their knowledge. Bards
        form loose associations, which they call colleges, to
        facilitate their gatherings and preserve their traditions.
        <br>
        <br>
        At <b>3rd level</b>, you delve into the advanced techniques of
        a bard college of your choice: the College of Lore or the
        College of Valor. <b>Your choice grants you features at 3rd level
        and again at 6th and 14th level.</b>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="bardCollegeOfLoreAbilityList">
        <item>College Of Lore</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiencies</item>
        <item>Cutting Words</item>
        <item>Additional Magical Secrets</item>
        <item>Peerless Skill</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bardCollegeOfLoreAbilityDescription">
        <item>College of Lore</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you join the College of Lore at <b>3rd level</b>, you gain
            proficiency with three skills of your choice.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also at <b>3rd level</b>, you learn how to use your wit to
            distract, confuse, and otherwise sap the confidence and
            competence of others. When a creature that you can
            see within 60 feet of you makes an attack roll, an ability
            check, or a damage roll, you can use your reaction to
            expend one of your uses of Bardic Inspiration, rolling
            a Bardic Inspiration die and subtracting the number
            rolled from the creature’s roll. You can choose to use
            this feature after the creature makes its roll, but before
            the DM determines whether the attack roll or ability
            check succeeds or fails, or before the creature deals its
            damage. The creature is immune if it can’t hear you or if
            it’s immune to being charmed.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, you learn two spells of your choice from any
            class. A spell you choose must be of a level you can cast,
            as shown on the Bard table, or a cantrip. The chosen
            spells count as bard spells for you but don’t count
            against the number of bard spells you know.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>14th level</b>, when you make an ability check,
            you can expend one use of Bardic Inspiration. Roll a
            Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to
            your ability check. You can choose to do so after you roll
            the die for the ability check, but before the DM tells you
            whether you succeed or fail.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bardCollegeOfValorAbilitiesList">
        <item>College of Valor</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiecies</item>
        <item>Combat Inspiration</item>
        <item>Extra Attack</item>
        <item>Battle Magic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="bardCollegeOfValorAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>College of Valor</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you join the College of Valor at <b>3rd level</b>, you
            gain proficiency with medium armor, shields, and
            martial weapons.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also at <b>3rd level</b>, you learn to inspire others in battle.
            A creature that has a Bardic Inspiration die from you
            can roll that die and add the number rolled to a weapon
            damage roll it just made.
            <br>
            <br>
            Alternatively, when an attack
            roll is made against the creature, it can use its reaction
            to roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number
            rolled to its AC against that attack, after seeing the roll
            but before knowing whether it hits or misses.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, you can attack twice, instead of
            once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>14th level</b>, you have mastered the art of weaving
            spellcasting and weapon use into a single harmonious
            act. When you use your action to cast a bard spell, you
            can make one weap on attack as a bonus action.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //------------------------------CLERIC---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    <string-array name="clericAbilitiesList">
        <item>Cleric Abilities</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Turn Undead</item>
        <item>Destroy Undead</item>
        <item>Divine Intervention</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Cleric Abilities Description</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>2nd level</b>, you gain the ability to channel divine
            energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel
            magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn
            Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some
            domains grant you additional effects as you advance in
            levels, as noted in the domain description.
            <br>
            <br>
            When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose
            which effect to create. You must then finish a short or
            long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.
            <br>
            <br>
            Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws.
            When you use such an effect from this class, the DC
            equals your cleric spell save DC.
            <br>
            <br>
            Beginning at <b>6th level</b>, you can use your Channel
            Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at <b>18th level.</b>
            you can use it three times between rests. When you finish
            a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a
            prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see
            or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom
            saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is
            turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.
            <br>
            <br>
            A turned creature must spend its turns trying to move
            as far away from you as it can, and it can’t willingly
            move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take
            reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action
            or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from
            moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use
            the Dodge action.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item><![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>5th level</b>, when an undead fails its saving
            throw against your Turn Undead feature, the creature is
            instantly destroyed if its challenge rating is at or below a
            certain threshold, as shown in the table below.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Destroy Undead of Cr:</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            Lvl 5th:\t\t\t1/2 or lower
            <br>
            Lvl 8th:\t\t\t\t\t\t1 or lower
            <br>
            Lvl 11th:\t\t\t\t2 or lower
            <br>
            Lvl 14th:\t\t\t\t3 or lower
            <br>
            Lvl 17th:\t\t\t\t4 or lower
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>10th level</b>, you can call on your deity to
            intervene on your behalf when your need is great.
            <br>
            <br>
            Imploring your deity’s aid requires you to use your
            action. Describe the assistance you seek, and roll
            percentile dice. If you roll a number equal to or lower
            than your cleric level, your deity intervenes. The DM
            chooses the nature of the intervention; the effect of any
            cleric spell or cleric domain spell would be appropriate.
            <br>
            If your deity intervenes, you can’t use this feature
            again for 7 days. Otherwise, you can use it again after
            you finish a long rest.
            <br>
            <b>At 20th level, your call for intervention succeeds
            automatically, no roll required.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="clericDivineDomainsTitle">
        Divine Domains
    </string>

    <string name="clericDivineDomainsDescription">
        <![CDATA[
        In a pantheon, every deity has influence over different
        aspects of mortal life and civilization, called a deity’s
        domain. All the domains over which a deity has
        influence are called the deity’s portfolio. For example,
        the portfolio of the Greek god Apollo includes the
        domains of Know ledge, Life, and Light. As a cleric, you
        choose one aspect of your deity’s portfolio to emphasize,
        and you are granted powers related to that domain.
        <br>
        <br>
        Your choice might correspond to a particular sect
        dedicated to your deity. Apollo, for example, could be
        worshiped in one region as Phoebus (“radiant”). Apollo,
        emphasizing his influence over the Light domain,
        and in a different place as Apollo Acesius (“healing”),
        emphasizing his association with the Life domain.
        Alternatively, your choice of domain could simply be a
        matter of personal preference, the aspect of the deity
        that appeals to you most.
        <br>
        <br>
        Each domain’s description gives examples of deities
        who have influence over that domain. Gods are included
        from the worlds of the Forgotten Realms, Greyhawk,
        Dragon lance, and Eberron campaign settings, as well as
        from the Celtic, Greek, Norse, and Egyptian pantheons
        of antiquity.
        <br>
        <br>
        Choose one domain related to your deity: Knowledge,
        Life, Light, Nature, Tempest, Trickery, or War. Each
        domain is detailed at the end of the class description,
        and each one provides examples of gods associated
        with it. Your choice grants you domain spells and other
        features when you choose it at 1st level. It also grants
        you additional ways to use Channel Divinity when you
        gain that feature at 2nd level, and additional benefits at
        6th, 8th, and 17th levels.
        <br>
        <br>
        Each domain has a list of spells—its domain spells—
        that you gain at the cleric levels noted in the domain
        description. Once you gain a domain spell, you always
        have it prepared, and it doesn’t count against the
        number of spells you can prepare each day.
        If you have a domain spell that doesn’t appear on the
        cleric spell list, the spell is nonetheless a cleric spell for you.
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="clericKnowledgeDomainAbilitiesList">
        <item>Knowledge Domain</item>
        <item>Knowledge Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Blessing of Knowledge</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Knowledge of the Ages</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Read Thoughts</item>
        <item>Potent Spellcasting</item>
        <item>Visions of the Past</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericKnowledgeDomainAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Knowledge Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Lvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tSpell Name:\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t command,\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tidentify\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t taugury,\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tsuggestion
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t speak with dead,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tnondetection
            <br>
            <br>
            7th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t tarcane eye,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tconfusion
            <br>
            <br>
            9th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t legend lore,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tscrying
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>1st level</b>, you learn two languages of your choice.
            You also become proficient in your choice of two of the
            follow in skills: <b>Arcana, History, Nature, or Religion.</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            Your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check
            you make that uses either of those skills.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to tap into a divine well of knowledge. As an action,
            you choose one skill or tool. For 10 minutes, you have
            proficiency with the chosen skill or tool.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity to read a
            creature’s thoughts. You can then use your access to the
            creature’s mind to command it.
            <br>
            <br>
            As an action, choose one creature that you can see
            within 60 feet of you. That creature must make a
            Wisdom saving throw. If the creature succeeds on the
            saving throw, you can’t use this feature on it again until
            you finish a long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            If the creature fails its save, you can read its surface
            thoughts (those foremost in its mind, reflecting its
            current emotions and what it is actively thinking
            about) when it is within 60 feet of you. This effect lasts
            for 1 minute.
            <br>
            <br>
            During that time, you can use your action to end this
            effect and cast the suggestion spell on the creature
            without expending a spell slot. The target automatically
            fails its saving throw against the spell.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>8th level</b>, you add your Wisdom modifier to
            the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>17th level</b>, you can call up visions of the
            past that relate to an object you hold or your immediate
            surroundings. You spend at least 1 minute in meditation
            and prayer, then receive dream like, shadowy glimpses
            of recent events. You can meditate in this way for a
            number of minutes equal to your Wisdom score and
            must maintain concentration during that time, as if you
            were casting a spell.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until
            you finish a short or long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Object Reading.</b> Holding an object as you meditate,
            you can see visions of the object’s previous owner.
            After meditating for 1 minute, you learn how the owner
            acquired and lost the object, as well as the most recent
            significant event involving the object and that owner.
            If the object was owned by another creature in the
            recent past (within a number of days equal to your
            Wisdom score), you can spend 1 additional minute
            for each owner to learn the same information about
            that creature.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Area Reading.</b> As you meditate, you see visions
            of recent events in your immediate vicinity (a room ,
            street, tunnel, clearing, or the like, up to a 50-foot cube),
            going back a number of days equal to your Wisdom
            score. For each minute you meditate, you learn about
            one significant event, beginning with the most recent.
            Significant events typically involve powerful emotions,
            such as battles and betrayals, marriages and murders,
            births and funerals. However, they might also include
            more mundane events that are nevertheless important
            in your current situation.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericLifeDomainAbilitiesList">
        <item>Life Domain</item>
        <item>Life Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiency</item>
        <item>Disciple of Life</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Preserve Life</item>
        <item>Blessed Healer</item>
        <item>Divine Strike</item>
        <item>Supreme Healing</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericLifeDomainAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Life Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Lvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tSpells:\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t bless,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tcure wounds
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t\t lesser restoration,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tspiritual weapon
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t\t beacon of hope,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\trevivify
            <br>
            <br>
            7th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t death ward,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tguardian of faith
            <br>
            <br>
            9th \t\t\t\t mass cure wounds
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\traise dead
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you choose this domain at <b>1st level</b>, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also starting at <b>1st level</b>, your healing spells are more
            effective. Whenever you use a spell of 1st level or higher
            to restore hit points to a creature, the creature regains
            additional hit points equal to 2+ the spell’s level.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to heal the badly injured.
            <br>
            <br>
            As an action, you present your holy symbol and
            evoke healing energy that can restore a number of hit
            points equal to five times your cleric level. Choose any
            creatures within 30 feet of you, and divide those hit
            points among them. This feature can restore a creature
            to no more than half of its hit point maximum . You can’t
            use this feature on an undead or a construct.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>6th level</b>, the healing spells you cast on
            others heal you as well. When you cast a spell of 1st
            level or higher that restores hit points to a creature
            other than you, you regain hit points equal to 2+ the
            spell’s level.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>8th level</b>, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon
            strikes with divine energy. Once on each of your turns
            when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can
            cause the attack to deal an extra 1d8 radiant damage to
            the target. <b>When you reach 14th level, the extra damage
            in creases to 2d8.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>17th level</b>, when you would normally roll
            one or more dice to restore hit points with a spell, you
            instead use the highest number possible for each die.
            For example, instead of restoring 2d6 hit points to a
            creature, you restore 12.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="clericLightDomainAbilityList">
        <item>Light Domain</item>
        <item>Light Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Bonus Cantrip</item>
        <item>Warding Flare</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Radiance of the Dawn</item>
        <item>Improved Flare</item>
        <item>Potent Spellcasting</item>
        <item>Corona of Light</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericLightDomainAbilityDescription">
        <item>Light Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>\t\tLvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Spells:\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t burning hands,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t faerie fire
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t flaming sphere,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t scorching ray
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t daylight,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t fireball
            <br>
            <br>
            \t7th \t\t\t\t\t\t guardian of faith,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t wall of fire
            <br>
            <br>
            9th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t flame strike,\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t scrying
            ]]>
        </item>

        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you choose this domain at <b>1st level</b>, you gain the
            light cantrip if you don’t already know it.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also at <b>1st level</b>, you can interpose divine light between
            yourself and an attacking enemy. When you are attacked
            by a creature within 30 feet of you that you can see,
            you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on
            the attack roll, causing light to flare before the attacker
            before it hits or misses. An attacker that can’t be blinded
            is immune to this feature.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can use this feature a number of times equal to
            your Wisdom modifier (a minim um of once). You regain
            all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to harness sunlight, banishing darkness and dealing
            radiant damage to your foes.
            <br>
            <br>
            As an action, you present your holy symbol, and any
            magical darkness within 30 feet of you is dispelled.
            Additionally, each hostile creature within 30 feet of
            you must make a Constitution saving throw. A creature
            takes radiant damage equal to 2d10 + your cleric level
            on a failed saving throw, and half as much damage on a
            successful one. A creature that has total cover from you
            is not affected.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, you can also use your Warding
            Flare feature when a creature that you can see within
            30 feet of you attacks a creature other than you.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>8th level</b>, you add your Wisdom modifier to
            the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>17th level</b>, you can use your action to activate
            an aura of sunlight that lasts for 1 minute or until you
            dismiss it using another action. You emit bright light in
            a 60-foot radius and dim light 30 feet beyond that. Your
            enemies in the bright light have disadvantage on saving
            throws against any spell that deals fire or radiant damage.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericNatureDomainAbilityList">
        <item>Nature Domain</item>
        <item>Nature Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Acolyte of Nature</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiency</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Charm Animals and Plants</item>
        <item>Dampen Elements</item>
        <item>Divine Strike</item>
        <item> Master of Nature</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericNatureDomainAbilityDescription">
        <item>Nature Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Lvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Spells:\t\t\t\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t animal friendship,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t speak with animals
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t barskin,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t spikegrow
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t plant growth,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t wind wall
            <br>
            <br>
            \t7th \t\t\t\t\t dominate beast,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t grasping vine
            <br>
            <br>
            \t9th \t\t\t\t\t\t inspect plague,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t tree stride
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>1st level</b>, you learn one druid cantrip of your choice.
            You also gain proficiency in one of the following skills of
            your choice: Animal Handling, Nature, or Survival.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also at <b>1st level</b>, you gain proficiency with heavy armor.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to charm animals and plants.
            <br>
            <br>
            As an action, you present your holy symbol and invoke
            the name of your deity. Each beast or plant creature that
            can see you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom
            saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is
            charmed by you for 1 minute or until it takes damage.
            While it is charmed by you, it is friendly to you and other
            creatures you designate.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level<b>, w hen you or a creature within 30
            feet of you takes acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder
            damage, you can use your reaction to grant resistance to
            the creature against that instance of the damage.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>8th level</b>, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy.
            Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause
            the attack to deal an extra 1d8 cold, fire, or lightning damage (your choice) to the
            target. When you reach  14th level, the extra damage increases to 2d8.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>17th level</b>, you gain the ability to command animals
            and plant creatures. While creatures are charmed by
            your Charm Animals and Plants feature, you can take
            a bonus action on your turn to verbally command what
            each of those creatures will do on its next turn.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="clericTempestDomainAbilityList">
        <item>Tempest Domain</item>
        <item>Tempest Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiency</item>
        <item>Wrath of the Storm</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Destructive Wraith</item>
        <item>Thunderbolt Strike</item>
        <item> Divine Strike</item>
        <item>Stormborn</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericTempestDomainAbilityDescription">
        <item>Tempest Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Lvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Spells:\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t fog cloud, \t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t thunderwave
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t gust of wind,\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t shatter
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t call ligtning, \t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            sleet storm
            <br>
            <br>
            7th \t\t\t\t\t control water,\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\tice storm
            <br>
            <br>
            9th \t\t\t\t destructive wave,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tinsect plague
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At  <b>1st level</b>, you gain proficiency with martial weapons and heavy armor
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Also at <b>1st level</b>, you can thunderously rebuke attackers.
            When a creature within 5 feet of you that you can see
            hits you with an attack, you can use your reaction to
            cause the creature to make a Dexterity saving throw.
            The creature takes 2d8 lightning or thunder damage
            (your choice) on a failed saving throw, and half as much
            damage on a successful one.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can use this feature a number of times equal to
            your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain
            all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to wield the power of the storm with unchecked ferocity.
            <br>
            <br>
            When you roll lightning or thunder damage, you can
            use your Channel Divinity to deal maximum damage,
            instead of rolling.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, when you deal lightning damage to a Large
            or smaller creature, you can also push it up to 10 feet
            away from you.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>8th level</b>, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy.
            Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause
            the attack to deal an extra  1d8 thunder damage to the target. <b>When you reach  14th level,
            the extra damage increases to 2d8.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>17th level,</b> you have a flying speed equal to
            your current walking speed whenever you are not
            underground or indoors.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="clericTrickeryDomainAbilityList">
        <item>Trickery Domain</item>
        <item>Trickery Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Blessing of the Trickster</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Invoke Duplicity</item>
        <item>Cloak of Shadows</item>
        <item>Divine Strike</item>
        <item>Improved Duplicity</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericTrickeryDomainAbilityDescription">
        <item>Trickery Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Lvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tSpells:\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t charm person,\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tdisguise self
            <br>
            <br>
            3rd \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t mirror image,\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tpass without a trace
            <br>
            <br>
            5th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t blink,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\tdispel magic
            <br>
            <br>
            7th \t\t\t\t\t\t dimension door,\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t polymorph
            <br>
            <br>
            9th \t\t\t\t dominate person,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t modify memory
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting when you choose this domain at <b>1st level</b>, you
            can use your action to touch a willing creature other
            than yourself to give it advantage on Dexterity (Stealth)
            checks. This blessing lasts for 1 hour or until you use
            this feature again.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to create an illusory duplicate of yourself.
            <br>
            <br>
            As an action, you create a perfect illusion of
            yourself that lasts for 1 minute, or until you lose your
            concentration (as if you were concentrating on a spell).
            The illusion appears in an unoccupied space that you
            can see within 30 feet of you. As a bonus action on your
            turn, you can move the illusion up to 30 feet to a space
            you can see, but it must remain within 120 feet of you.
            <br>
            <br>
            For the duration, you can cast spells as though you
            were in the illusion’s space, but you must use your own
            senses. Additionally, when both you and your illusion
            are within 5 feet of a creature that can see the illusion,
            you have advantage on attack rolls against that creature,
            given how distracting the illusion is to the target.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, you can u se your Channel
            Divinity to vanish.
            As an action, you become invisible until the end of your
            next turn. You become visible if you attack or cast a spell.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>8th level</b>, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with poison—a
            gift from your deity. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a
            weapon attack, you can cause the attack to deal an extra  1d8 poison damage to the target.
            <b>When you reach  14th level, the extra damage increases to 2d8.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>17th level</b>, you can create up to four duplicates
            of yourself, instead of one, w hen you use Invoke
            Duplicity. As a bonus action on your turn, you can
            move any number of them up to 30 feet, to a maximum
            range of 120 feet.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericWarDomainAbilityList">
        <item>War Domain</item>
        <item>War Domain Spells</item>
        <item>Bonus Profitiency</item>
        <item>War Priest</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: Guided Strike</item>
        <item>Channel Divinity: War Gods Blessing</item>
        <item>Divine Strike</item>
        <item>Avatar of Battle</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="clericWarDomainAbilityDescription">
        <item>War Domain</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>\t\tLvl: \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tSpells:\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            \n1st \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t divine favor,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tshield of faith
            <br>
            <br>
            \n3rd \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t tmagic weapon,\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tspiritual weapon
            <br>
            <br>
            \n5th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tcrusaders mantle,\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tspirit guardian
            <br>
            <br>
            \n7th \t\t\t\tfreedom of movement,
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tstoneskin<br>
            <br>
            <br>
            \n9th \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t flame strike,\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t
            <br>
            \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\thold monster
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>1st level</b>, you gain proficiency with martial weapons and heavy armor.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            From <b>1st level</b>, your god delivers bolts of inspiration to
            you while you are engaged in battle. When you use the
            Attack action, you can make one weapon attack as a
            bonus action.
            \n\nYou can use this feature a number of times equal to
            your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain
            all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can use your Channel Divinity
            to strike with supernatural accuracy. When you make
            an attack roll, you can use your Channel Divinity to gain
            a +10 bonus to the roll. You make this choice after you
            see the roll, but before the DM says whether the attack
            hits or misses.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>6th level</b>, when a creature within 30 feet of you
            makes an attack roll, you can use your reaction to grant
            that creature a +10 bonus to the roll, using your Channel
            Divinity. You make this choice after you see the roll, but
            before the DM says whether the attack hits or misses.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>8th level</b>, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon strikes with divine energy.
            Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can cause the
            attack to deal an extra 1d8 damage of the same type dealt by the weapon to the target.
            When you reach 14th level, the extra damage increases to 2d8.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>17th level</b>, you gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing,
            and slashing damage from non magical weapons.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //------------------------------DRUID---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

    <string-array name="druidAbilityList">
        <item>Druid Abilities</item>
        <item>Druidic</item>
        <item>Wild Shape</item>
        <item>Timeless Body</item>
        <item>Beast Spells</item>
        <item>Archdruid</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="druidAbilityDescription">
        <item>Druid Abilities</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages.
            You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message.
            Others spot the message\'s presence with a successful DC  15 Wisdom (Perception)
            check but can\'t decipher it without magic.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at 2nd level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before.
            You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            Your druid level determines the beasts you can transform into,
            as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example,
            you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower
            that doesn\'t have a flying or swimming speed
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Beast Shapes:</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 2
            <br>
            <b>CR:</b> 1/4
            <br>
            <b>Limitations:</b> No flying/swimming speed
            <br>
            <b>Example:</b> Wolf
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 4
            <br>
            <b>CR:</b> 1/2
            <br>
            <b>Limitations:</b> No flying/swimming speed
            <br>
            <b>Example:</b> Crocodile
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 8
            <br>
            <b>CR:</b> 1
            <br>
            <b>Limitations:</b> -
            <br>
            <b>Example:</b> Giant Eagle
            <br>
            <br>
            You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal
            to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your
            normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can
            revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your
            turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 0 hit points, or die
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>While you are transformed, the following rules apply:</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast,
            but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence,
            Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill
            and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature.
            If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block
            is higher than yours, use the creature\'s bonus instead of yours. If the creature
            has any legendary or lair actions, you can\'t use them
            <br>
            <br>
            When you transform, you assume the beast\'s hit points and Hit Dice.
            When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points
            you had before you transformed. However, if you revert as a result of dropping
            to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example,
            if you take  10 damage in animal form and have only 1 hit point left, you revert
            and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn\'t
            reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren\'t knocked unconscious
            <br>
            <br>
            You can\'t cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that
            requires hands is limited to the capabilities of your beast form.
            Transforming doesn\'t break your concentration on a spell you\'ve already cast,
            however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell,
            such as call lightning, that you\'ve already cast
            <br>
            <br>
            You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race,
            or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so.
            However, you can\'t use any of your special senses, such as darkvision,
            unless your new form also has that sense
            <br>
            <br>
            You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space,
            merges into your new form, or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal,
            but the DM decides whether it is practical for the new form to wear a piece of equipment,
            based on the creature\'s shape and size. Your equipment doesn\'t
            change size or shape to match the new form, and any equipment
            that the new form can\'t wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it.
            Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
        <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>18th level</b>, the primal magic that you wield
            causes you to age more slowly. For every 10 years that pass, your body ages only 1 year
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
        <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>18th level</b>, you can cast many of your druid spells
            in any shape you assume using W ild Shape. You can perform the somatic
            and verbal components of a druid spell while in a beast shape,
            but you aren\'t able to provide material components
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
        <![CDATA[
            At <b>20th level</b>, you can use your Wild Shape an unlimited number of times.
            <br>
            <br>
            Additionally, you can ignore the verbal and somatic components of your druid spells,
            as well as any material components that lack a cost and aren\'t consumed by a spell.
            You gain this benefit in both your normal shape and your beast shape from Wild Shape.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="druidDruidCirclesName">Druid Circles</string>

    <string name="druidDruidCirclesDescription">
        <![CDATA[
        Though their organization is invisible to most outsiders,
        druids are part of a society that spans the land, ignoring
        political borders. All druids are nominally members of this
        druidic society, though som e individuals are so isolated that
        they have never seen any high-ranking members of the society or participated
        in druidic gatherings. Druids recognize each other as brothers and sisters.
        Like creatures of the wilderness, however, druids sometimes compete with or even prey on each other.
        <br>
        <br>
        At a local scale, druids are organized into circles that share certain perspectives on nature, balance, and the way of the druid.
        <br>
        <br>
        At 2nd level, you choose to identify with a circle of druids: the Circle of the Land or the Circle of the Moon, 
        both detailed at the end of the class description. Your choice grants you features at 2nd level and again at 6th,  10th, and  14th level.
        ]]>
    </string>
    
    <string-array name="druidCircleOfLandAbilitiesList">
        <item>Circle of Land</item>
        <item>Bonus Cantrip</item>
        <item>Natural Recovery</item>
        <item>Circle Spells</item>
        <item>Lands Stride</item>
        <item>Natures Ward</item>
        <item>Natures Sanctuary</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="druidCircleOfLandAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Circle of Land</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
             When you choose this circle at <b>2nd level</b>, you learn one additional druid cantrip of your choice.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can regain some of your magical energy by
            sitting in meditation and communing with nature. During a short rest,
            you choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a
            combined level that is equal to or less than half your druid level (rounded up),
            and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher. You can\'t use this feature
            again until you finish a long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            For example, when you are a 4th-level druid, you can recover up to two levels
            worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level slot or two  1st-level slots.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Your mystical connection to the land infuses you with the
            ability to cast certain spells. At <b>3rd, 5th, 7th, and 9th
            level</b> you gain access to circle spells connected to the
            land where you became a druid. Choose that land—arctic,
            coast, desert, forest, grassland, mountain, swamp, or
            Underdark—and consult the associated list of spells.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you gain access to a circle spell,
            you always have it prepared, and it doesn\'t
            count against the number of spells you can prepare each day.
            If you gain access to a spell that doesn\'t appear on the druid
            spell list, the spell is nonetheless a druid spell for you
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Arctic</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>hold person, spike growth
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>sleet storm, slow
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>freedom of movement, ice storm
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>commune with nature, cone of cold
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Coast</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>mirror image, misty step
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>water breathing, water walk
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>control water, freedom of movement
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>conjure elemental, scrying
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Desert</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>blur, silence
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>create food and water, protection from energy
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>blight, hallucinatory terrain
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>insect plague, wall of stone
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Forest</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>barskin, spider climb
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>call lightning, plant growth
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>divination, freedom of movement
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>commune with nature, tree stride
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Grassland</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>invisibility, pass without a trace
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>daylight, haste
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>freedom of movement, divination
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>dream, insect plague
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Mountain</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>spider climb, spike growth
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>lightning bolt, meld into stone
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>stone shape, stoneskin
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>passwall, wall of stone
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b><u>Swamp</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>darkness, Melfs acid arrow
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>water walk, stinking cloud
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>freedom of movement, locate creature
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>insect plague, scrying
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
             <b><u>Underdark</u></b>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 3rd
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>spider climb, web
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 5th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>gaseous form, stinking cloud
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 7th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>greater invisibility, stone shape
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Level:</b> 9th
            <br>
            <b>Circle Spells: </b>cloudkill, insect plague
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, moving through nonmagical
            difficult terrain costs you no extra movement.
            You can also pass through nonmagical plants without
            being slowed by them and without taking damage from them
            if they have thorns, spines, or a similar hazard.
            <br>
            <br>
            In addition, you have advantage on saving throws
            against plants that are magically created or manipulated to
            impede movement, such those created by the entangle spell
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you reach  <b>10th level</b>, you can\'t be
            charmed or frightened by elementals or fey,
            and you are immune to poison and disease.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you reach  <b>14th level</b>, creatures of the natural world sense
            your connection to nature and become hesitant to attack you.
            When a beast or plant creature attacks you, that creature must
            make a Wisdom saving throw against your druid spell save DC.
            On a failed save, the creature must choose a different target,
            or the attack automatically misses. On a successful save, the
            creature is immune to this effect for 24 hours.
            <br>
            <br>
            The creature is aware of this effect before it makes its attack against you.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="druidCircleOfMoonAbilityList">
        <item>Circle of the Moon</item>
        <item>Combat Wild Shape</item>
        <item>Circle Forms</item>
        <item>Primal Strike</item>
        <item>Elemental Wild Shape</item>
        <item>Thousand Forms</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="druidCircleOfMoonAbilityDescription">
        <item>Circle of the Moon</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            When you choose this circle at <b>2nd level</b>,
            you gain the ability to use Wild Shape on your
            turn as a bonus action, rather than as an action.
            <br>
            <br>
            Additionally, while you are transformed by
            Wild Shape, you can use a bonus action to
            expend one spell slot to regain  1d8 hit points per level of the spell slot expended.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            The rites of your circle grant you the ability to transform into more
            dangerous animal forms. Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Wild
            Shape to transform into a beast with a challenge rating as high as
            1 (you ignore the Max. CR column of the Beast Shapes table, but must abide by the
            other limitations there).
            <br>
            <br>
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, you can transform into a beast with a challenge rating as
            high as your druid level divided by 3, rounded down.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>6th level</b>, your attacks in beast form count as magical
            for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to nonmagical attacks and damage.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At  <b>10th level</b>, you can expend two uses of Wild Shape
            at the same time to transform into an air elemental,
            an earth elemental, a fire elemental, or a water elemental.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            By <b>14th level</b>, you have learned to use magic to alter your physical
            form in more subtle ways. You can cast the alter self spell at will.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    //------------------------------FIGHTER---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

    <string-array name="fighterAbilitiesList">
        <item>Fighter Abilities</item>
        <item>Fighting Style</item>
        <item>Second Wind</item>
        <item>Action Surge</item>
        <item>Indomitable</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighterAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Fighter Abilities</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            You adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty.
            Choose one of the following options. You can\'t take a
            Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>ARCHERY</b>
            <br>
            You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>DEFENSE</b>
            <br>
            While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>DUELING</b>
            <br>
            When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>GREAT WEAPON FIGHTING</b>
            <br>
            W hen you roll a  1  or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a
            melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can
            reroll the die and must use the new roll, even if the new
            roll is a 1 or a 2. The weapon must have the two-handed
            or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>PROTECTION</b>
            <br>
            W hen a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that
            is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose
            disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>TWO-WEAPON FIGHTING</b>
            <br>
            When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm.
            On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to  1d10 + your fighter level.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>2nd level</b>, you can push yourself beyond your normal limits for a moment.
            On your turn, you can take one additional action on top of your regular action and a possible bonus action.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.
            <b>Starting at  17th level, you can use it twice before a rest, but only once on the same turn.</b>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>9th level</b>, you can reroll a saving throw that you fail.
            If you do so, you must use the new roll, and you can\'t use this feature again until you finish a long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can use this feature twice between long rests
            starting at 13th level and three times between long rests starting at  17th level.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="fighterMartialArchetype">
        Martial Archetype
    </string>

    <string name="fighterMartialArchetypeDescription">
        <![CDATA[
        Different fighters choose different approaches to perfecting their fighting prowess. 
        The martial archetype you choose to emulate reflects your approach.
        <br>
        <br>
        At <b>3rd level</b>, you choose an archetype that you strive to emulate in your combat styles 
        and techniques. Choose Champion, Battle Master, or Eldritch Knight,  all detailed at the 
        end of the class description. The archetype you choose grants you features at 3rd level and 
        again at <b>7th, 10th,  15th, and  18th level.</b>
        ]]>
    </string>
    
    <string-array name="fighterChampionAbilities">
        <item>Champion</item>
        <item>Improved Critical</item>
        <item>Remarkable Athlete</item>
        <item>Additional Fighting Style</item>
        <item>Superior Critical</item>
        <item>Survivor</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighterChampionAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Champion</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning when you choose this archetype at <b>3rd level</b>,
            your weapon attacks score a critical hit on a roll of 19 or 20.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>7th level</b>, you can add half your proficiency bonus (round up)
            to any Strength, Dexterity, or Constitution check you make that doesn\'t already use
            your proficiency bonus.
            <br>
            <br>
            In addition, when you make a running long jump, the distance you can cover increases
            by a number of feet equal to your Strength modifier.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>10th level</b>, you can choose a second option from theFighting Style class feature.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>15th level</b>, your weapon attacks score a critical hit on a roll of 18-20.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>18th level</b>, you attain the pinnacle of resilience in battle.
            At the start of each of your turns, you regain hit points equal to 5 + your
            Constitution modifier if you have no more than half of your hit points left. You don\'t
            gain this benefit if you have 0 hit points.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighterBattleMasterAbilities">
        <item>Battle Master</item>
        <item>Combat Superiority</item>
        <item>Student of War</item>
        <item>Know Your Enemy</item>
        <item>Improved Combat Superiority</item>
        <item>Relentless</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighterBattleMasterAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Battle Master</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            W hen you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you learn maneuvers that are fueled by special dice called superiority dice.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Maneuvers</b>
            <br>
            Maneuvers. You learn three maneuvers of your choice, which are detailed under “Maneuvers”
            below. Many maneuvers enhance an attack in som e way. You can use only one maneuver per attack.
            <br>
            <br>
            You learn two additional maneuvers of your choice at 7th,  10th, and  15th level.
            Each time you learn new maneuvers, you can also replace one maneuver you know with a different one.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Superiority Dice</b>
            <br>
            You have four superiority dice, which are d8s.
            A superiority die is expended when you use it. You regain all of your expended superiority dice when you finish a short or long rest.
            <br>
            <br>
            You gain another superiority die at 7th level and one more at  15th level.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Saving Throws</b>
            <br>
            Some of your maneuvers require your target to make a saving throw to resist the maneuver\'s effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Maneuver Save DC =</b> 8 + your profitiency bonus + your Strength or Dexterity mod. (your choice)
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>..::MANEUVERS::.</b>
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Commanders Strike</b>
            <br>
            When you take the Attack action on your turn, you can forgo one
            of your attacks and use a bonus action to direct one of your companions to strike.
            When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you and expend one superiority die.
            That creature can immediately use its reaction to make one weapon attack, adding the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Disarming Attack</b>
            <br>
            When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt
            to disarm the target, forcing it to drop one item of your choice that it\'s holding. You add the
            superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll, and the target must make a Strength saving throw.
            On a failed save, it drops the object you choose. The object lands at its feet.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Distracting Strike</b>
            <br>
            When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to
            distract the creature, giving your allies an opening. You add the superiority die to the
            attack\'s damage roll. The next attack roll against the target by an attacker other than you
            has advantage if the attack is made before the start of your next turn.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Evasive Footwork</b>
            <br>
            When you move, you can expend one superiority die, rolling the die and adding the number rolled to your AC until you stop moving.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Feinting Attack</b>
            <br>
            You can expend one superiority die and use a bonus action on your turn to feint,
            choosing one creature within 5 feet of you as your target. You have advantage on
            your next attack roll against that creature. If that attack hits, add the superiority
            die to the attack\'s damage roll.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Goading Attack</b>
            <br>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt
            to goad the target into attacking you. You add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll,
            and the target must make a Wisdom  saving throw. On a failed save, the target has disadvantage on
            all attack rolls against targets other than you until the end of your next turn.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Lunging Attack</b>
            <br>
            When you make a melee weapon attack on your turn,
            you can expend one superiority die to increase your reach for that
            attack by 5 feet. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Maneuvering Attack</b>
            <br>When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die
            to maneuver one of your comrades into a more advantageous position.
            You add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll, and you choose a friendly
            creature who can see or hear you. That creature can use its reaction to move up to
            half its speed without provoking opportunity attacks from the target of your attack.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Menacing Attack</b>
            <br>
            When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority
            die to attempt to frighten the target. You add the superiority die to the attack\'s
            damage roll, and the target must make a Wisdom  saving throw. On a failed save, it
            is frightened of you until the end of your next turn.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Parry</b>
            <br>When another creature damages you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction
            and expend one superiority die to reduce the damage by the number you roll on your
            superiority die + your Dexterity modifier.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Precision Attack</b>
            <br>When you make a weapon attack roll against a creature, you can expend one superiority
            die to add it to the roll. You can use this maneuver before or after making the attack roll,
            but before any effects of the attack are applied.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Pushing Attack</b>
            <br>
            W hen you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt
            to drive the target back. You add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll, and if the target
            is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you push the target up to
            15 feet away from you.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Rally</b>
            <br>
            On your turn, you can use a bonus action and expend one superiority die to bolster the resolve
            of one of your companions. When you do so, choose a friendly creature who can see or hear you.
            That creature gains temporary hit points equal to the superiority die roll + your Charisma modifier.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Riposte</b>
            <br>
            When a creature m isses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction and expend one superiority
            die to make a melee weapon attack against the creature. If you hit, you add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Sweeping Attack</b>
            <br>
            W hen you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt to damage another
            creature with the same attack. Choose another creature within 5 feet of the original target and within your reach.
            If the original attack roll would hit the second creature, it takes damage equal to the number you roll on your
            superiority die. The damage is of the same type dealt by the original attack.
            <br>
            <br>
            <b>Trip Attack</b>
            <br>
            When you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can expend one superiority die to attempt
            to knock the target down. You add the superiority die to the attack\'s damage roll, and if the
            target is Large or smaller, it must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you knock the target prone.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>3rd level</b>, you gain proficiency with one type of artisan\'s tools of your choice.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at <b>7th level</b>, if you spend at least  1  minute observing or interacting with another
            creature outside combat, you can learn certain information about its capabilities compared to your own.
            The DM tells you if the creature is your equal, superior, or inferior in regard to two of the
            following characteristics of your choice:
            <br>
            -Strength Score
            <br>
            -Dexterity Score,
            <br>
            -Constitution Score,
            <br>
            -Armor Class,
            <br>
            -Current hit points,
            <br>
            -Total class level (if any),
            <br>
            -Fighter class level (if any)
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>10th level</b>, your superiority dice turn into d10s. At18th level, they turn into d12s.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at  <b>15th level</b>, when you roll initiative
            and have no superiority dice remaining, you regain 1 superiority die.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="fighterEldrichtKnightAbilities">
        <item>Eldricht Knight</item>
        <item>Weapon Bound</item>
        <item>War Magic</item>
        <item>Eldritch Strike</item>
        <item>Arcane Charge</item>
        <item>Improved War Magic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fighterEldrichtKnightAbilitiesDescription">
        <item>Eldricht Knight</item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>3rd level</b>, you learn a ritual that creates a magical bond between
            yourself and one weapon. You perform the ritual over the course of 1 hour,
            which can be done during a short rest. The weapon must be within your reach throughout the ritual,
            at the conclusion of which you touch the weapon and forge the bond.
            <br>
            <br>
            Once you have bonded a weapon to yourself, you can\'t be disarmed of that weapon unless you
            are incapacitated. If it is on the same plane of existence, you can summon that weapon as a
            bonus action on your turn, causing it to teleport instantly to your hand.
            <br>
            <br>
            You can have up to two bonded weapons, but can summon only one at a time with your bonus action.
            If you attempt to bond with a third weapon, you must break the bond with one of the other two.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Beginning at <b>7th level</b>, when you use your action to cast a cantrip, you can make one weapon attack as a bonus action.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At <b>10th level</b>, you learn how to make your weapon strikes undercut a creature\'s resistance
            to your spells. W hen you hit a creature with a weapon attack, that creature has
            disadvantage on the next saving throw it makes against a spell you cast before the
            end of your next turn.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            At  <b>15th level</b>, you gain the ability to teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied
            space you can see when you use your Action Surge. You can teleport before or after the additional action.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Starting at  <b>18th level</b>, when you use your action to cast a spell, you can make one weapon attack as a bonus action.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>


    //-----MAX BUTTONS: 10
    //-----MAX BUTTONS PER SPEC: 7
    //-----MAX SPECS: 7

</resources>


