<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="classOverviewTitles">
        <item>Barbarian</item>
        <item>Bard</item>
        <item>Cleric</item>
        <item>Druid</item>
        <item>Fighter</item>
        <item>Monk</item>
        <item>Paladin</item>
        <item>Ranger</item>
        <item>Rogue</item>
        <item>Sorcerer</item>
        <item>Warlock</item>
        <item>Wizard</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="classOverviewSection1">
        <item> A tall human tribesman strides through a blizzard, draped in fur and hefting his axe.
            He laughs as he charges toward the frost giant who dared poach his people’s elk herd.
            \n\n
            For some, their rage springs from a communion with fierce animal spirits. Others
            draw from a roiling reservoir of anger at a world full of pain. For every barbarian,
            rage is a power that fuels not just a battle frenzy but also uncanny reflexes,
            resilience, and feats of strength.
        </item>

        <item>
            Humming as she traces her fingers over an ancient
            monument in a long-forgotten ruin, a half-elf in rugged
            leathers finds knowledge springing into her mind,
            conjured forth by the magic of her song — knowledge
            of the people who constructed the monument and the
            mythic saga it depicts.
            \n\n
            A stern human warrior bangs his sword rhythmically
            against his scale mail, setting the tempo for his war chant
            and exhorting his companions to bravery and heroism.
            The magic of his song fortifies and emboldens them.
            \n\n
            Laughing as she tunes her cittern, a gnome weaves
            her subtle magic over the assembled nobles, ensuring
            that her companions’ words will be well received.
            \n\n
            Whether scholar, skald, or scoundrel, a bard weaves
            magic through words and music to inspire allies,
            demoralize foes, manipulate minds, create
            illusions, and even heal wounds.
        </item>

        <item>
            Arms and eyes upraised toward the sun and a prayer
            on his lips, an elf begins to glow with an inner light that
            spills out to heal his battle-worn companions.
            \n\n
            Chanting a song of glory, a dwarf swings his axe
            in wide swaths to cut through the ranks of orcs
            arrayed against him, shouting praise to the gods with
            every foe\'s fall.
            \n\n
            Calling down a curse upon the forces of undeath, a
            human lifts her holy symbol as light pours from it to
            drive back the zombies crowding in on her companions.
            Clerics are intermediaries between the mortal world
            and the distant planes of the gods. As varied as the gods
            they serve, clerics strive to embody the handiwork of
            their deities. No ordinary priest, a cleric is imbued with
            divine magic.
        </item>

        <item> Holding high a gnarled staff wreathed with holly, an elf
            summons the fury of the storm and calls down explosive
            bolts of lightning to smite the torch-carrying orcs who
            threaten her forest.

            \n\nCrouching out of sight on a high tree branch in the
            form of a leopard, a human peers out of the jungle at the
            strange construction of a temple of Evil Elemental Air,
            keeping a close eye on the cultists\' activities.

            \n\nSwinging a blade formed of pure fire, a half-elf
            charges into a mass of skeletal soldiers, sundering
            the unnatural magic that gives the foul creatures the
            mocking semblance of life.

            \n\nWhether calling on the elemental forces of nature or
            emulating the creatures of the animal world, druids are
            an embodiment of nature\'s resilience, cunning, and fury.
            They claim no mastery over nature. Instead, they see
            them selves as extensions of nature\'s indomitable will.
        </item>

        <item>
            A human in clanging plate armor holds her shield
            before her as she runs toward the massed goblins. An
            elf behind her, clad in studded leather armor, peppers
            the goblins with arrows loosed from his exquisite
            bow. The half-orc nearby shouts orders, helping
            the two combatants coordinate their assault to the
            best advantage.

            \n\nA dwarf in chain mail interposes his shield between
            the ogre\'s club and his companion, knocking the deadly
            blow aside. His companion, a half-elf in scale armor,
            swings two scimitars in a blinding whirl as she circles
            the ogre, looking for a blind spot in its defenses.

            \n\nA gladiator fights for sport in an arena, a master with
            his trident and net, skilled at toppling foes and moving
            them around for the crowd\'s delight—and his own
            tactical advantage. His opponent\'s sword flares with
            blue light an instant before she sends lightning flashing
            forth to smite him.

            \n\nAll of these heroes are fighters, perhaps the most
            diverse class of characters in the worlds of Dungeons and
            Dragons. Questing knights, conquering overlords, royal
            champions, elite foot soldiers, hardened mercenaries,
            and bandit kings — as fighters, they all share an
            unparalleled mastery with weapons and armor, and a
            thorough knowledge of the skills of combat. And they
            are well acquainted with death, both meting it out and
            staring it defiantly in the face.
        </item>

        <item>
            Her fists a blur as they deflect an incoming hail of arrows,
            a half-elf springs over a barricade and throws herself
            into the massed ranks of hobgoblins on the other side.
            She whirls among them, knocking their blows aside and
            sending them reeling, until at last she stands alone.

            \n\nTaking a deep breath, a human covered in tattoos
            settles into a battle stance. As the first charging orcs
            reach him, he exhales and a blast of fire roars from his
            mouth, engulfing his foes.
            \n\nMoving with the silence of the night, a black-clad
            halfling steps into a shadow beneath an arch and
            emerges from another inky shadow on a balcony a
            stone\'s throw away. She slides her blade free of its cloth-
            wrapped scabbard and peers through the open window
            at the tyrant prince, so vulnerable in the grip of sleep.

            \n\nWhatever their discipline, monks are united in their
            ability to magically harness the energy that flows in
            their bodies. Whether channeled as a striking display
            of combat prowess or a subtler focus of defensive ability
            and speed, this energy infuses all that a monk does.
        </item>

        <item>
            Clad in plate armor that gleams in the sunlight despite
            the dust and grime of long travel, a human lays down
            her sword and shield and places her hands on a mortally
            wounded man. Divine radiance shines from her hands,
            the man’s wounds knit closed, and his eyes open wide
            with amazement.

            \n\nA dwarf crouches behind an outcrop, his black cloak
            making him nearly invisible in the night, and watches
            an orc warband celebrating its recent victory. Silently,
            he stalks into their midst and whispers an oath, and two
            orcs are dead before they even realize he is there.
            Silver hair shining in a shaft of light that seems to
            illuminate only him , an elf laughs with exultation. His
            spear flashes like his eyes as he jabs again and again
            at a twisted giant, until at last his light overcomes its
            hideous darkness.

            \n\nWhatever their origin and their mission, paladins are
            united by their oaths to stand against the forces of evil.
            Whether sworn before a god’s altar and the witness of
            a priest, in a sa cred glade before nature spirits and fey
            beings, or in a moment of desperation and grief with the
            dead as the only witness, a paladin’s oath is a powerful
            bond. It is a source of power that turns a devout warrior
            into a blessed champion.
        </item>

        <item>
            Rough and wild looking,
            a human stalks alone
            through the shadows of
            trees, hunting the orcs he
            knows are planning a raid
            on a nearby farm. Clutching
            a short sword in each hand,
            he becomes a whirlwind of
            steel, cutting down one enemy
            after another.

            \n\nAfter tumbling away from a cone of
            freezing air, an elf finds her feet and draws
            back her bow to loose an arrow at the white
            dragon. Shrugging off the wave of fear that emanates
            from the dragon like the cold of its breath, she sends
            one arrow after another to find the gaps between the
            dragon’s thick scales.

            \n\nHolding his hand high, a half-elf whistles to the hawk
            that circles high above him, calling the bird back to his
            side. Whispering instructions in Elvish, he points to
            the owlbear he\'s been tracking and sends the hawk to
            distract the creature while he readies his bow.

            \n\nFar from the bustle of cities and towns, past the
            hedges that shelter the most distant farms from the
            terrors of the wild, amid the dense-packed trees of
            trackless forests and across wide and empty plains,
            rangers keep their unending watch.
        </item>

        <item>
            Signaling for her companions to wait, a halfling creeps
            forward through the dungeon hall. She presses an ear
            to the door, then pulls out a set of tools and picks the
            lock in the blink of an eye. Then she disappears into
            the shadows as her fighter friend moves forward to kick
            the door open.

            \n\nA human lurks in the shadows of an alley while his
            accomplice prepares for her part in the ambush. When
            their target — a notorious slaver — passes the alleyway,
            the accomplice cries out, the slaver comes to investigate,
            and the assassin’s blade cuts his throat before he can
            make a sound.

            \n\nSuppressing a giggle, a gnome waggles her fingers
            and magically lifts the key ring from the guard’s belt.
            In a moment, the keys are in her hand, the cell door is
            open, and she and her companions are free to make
            their escape.

            \n\nRogues rely on skill, stealth, and their foes’
            vulnerabilities to get the upper hand in any situation.
            They have a knack for finding the solution to just about
            any problem , demonstrating a resourcefulness and
            versatility that is the cornerstone of any successful
            adventuring party.
        </item>

        <item>
            Golden eyes flashing, a human
            stretches out her hand and unleashes
            the dragonfire that burns in her veins.
            As an in ferno rages around her foes,
            leathery wings spread from her back and
            she takes to the air.

            \n\nLong hair whipped by a conjured wind,
            a half-elf spreads his arms wide and throws
            his head back. Lifting him momentarily off
            the ground, a wave of magic surges up in him,
            through him , and out from him in a mighty blast
            of lightning.

            \n\nCrouching behind a stalagmite, a halfling points a
            finger at a charging troglodyte. A blast of fire springs
            from her finger to strike the creature. She ducks back
            behind the rock formation with a grin, unaware that her
            wild magic has turned her skin bright blue.

            \n\nSorcerers carry a magical birthright conferred
            upon them by an exotic bloodline, some other worldly
            influence, or exposure to unknown cosmic forces.
            One can’t study sorcery as one learns a language, any
            more than one can learn to live a legendary life. No one
            chooses sorcery; the power chooses the sorcerer.
        </item>

        <item>
            With a pseudodragon curled on his shoulder, a young
            elf in golden robes smiles warmly, weaving a magical
            charm into his honeyed words and bending the palace
            sentinel to his will.

            \n\nAs flames spring to life in her hands, a wizened
            human whispers the secret name of her demonic patron,
            infusing her spell with fiendish magic.

            \n\nShifting his gaze between a battered tome and the
            od dalignment of the stars overhead, a wild - eyed tiefling
            chants the mystic ritual that will open a doorway to a
            distant world.

            \n\nWarlocks are seekers of the knowledge that lies
            hidden in the fabric of the multiverse. Through pacts
            made with mysterious beings of supernatural power,
            warlocks unlock magical effects both subtle and
            spectacular. Drawing on the ancient know ledge of
            beings such as fey nobles, demons, devils, hags, and
            alien entities of the Far Realm, warlock s piece together
            arcane secrets to bolster their own power.
        </item>

        <item>
             Clad in the silver robes that denote her station, an
            elf closes her eyes to shut out the distractions of the
            battlefield and begins her quiet chant. Fingers weaving
            in front of her, she completes her spell and launches a
            tiny bead of fire toward the enemy ranks, where it erupts
            into a conflagration that engulfs the soldiers.

            \n\nChecking and rechecking his work, a human scribes
            an intricate magic circle in chalk on the bare stone
            floor, then sprinkles powdered iron along every line and
            graceful curve. When the circle is complete, he drones a
            long incantation. A hole opens in space inside the circle,
            bringing a whiff of brimstone from the otherworldly
            plane beyond.

            \n\nCrouching on the floor in a dungeon intersection, a
            gnome tosses a handful of sm all bones in scribed with
            mystic symbols, muttering a few words of power over
            them. Closing his eyes to see the visions more clearly,
            he nods slowly, then opens his eyes and points down the
            passage to his left.

            \n\nWizards are supreme magic-users, defined and united
            as a class by the spells they cast. Drawing on the subtle
            weave of magic that permeates the cosmos, wizards cast
            spells of explosive fire, arcing lightning, subtle deception,
            and brute-force mind control. Their magic conjures
            monsters from other planes of existence, glimpses the
            future, or turns slain foes into zombies. Their mightiest
            spells change one substance into another, call meteors
            down from the sky, or open portals to other worlds.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="classOverviewSection2">
        <item>
            When creating a barbarian character, think about where your character com es from and
            his or her place in the world. Talk with your DM about an appropriate origin for your
            barbarian. Did you com e from a distant land, making you a stranger in the area of the
            campaign? Or is the campaign set in a rough-and-tumble frontier where barbarians are
            common? What led you to take up the adventuring life? Were you lured to settled lands
            by the promise of riches? Did you join forces with soldiers of those lands to face a
            shared threat? Did monsters or an invading horde drive you out of your homeland, making
            you a rootless refugee? Perhaps you were a prisoner of war, brought in chains to
            “civilized” lands and only now able to win your freedom. Or you might have been cast out
            from your people because of a crime you committed, a taboo you violated, or a coup that
            removed you from a position of authority.
        </item>

        <item>
            Bards thrive on stories, whether those stories are true
            or not. Your character’s background and motivations
            are not as important as the stories that he or she tells
            about them. Perhaps you had a secure and mundane
            childhood. There’s no good story to be told about that,
            so you might paint yourself as an orphan raised by a hag
            in a dismal swamp. Or your childhood might be worthy
            of a story. Some bards acquire their magical music
            through extraordinary means, including the inspiration
            of fey or other supernatural creatures.
            \n\n
            Did you serve an apprenticeship, studying under a
            master, following the more experienced bard until you
            were ready to strike out on your own? Or did you attend
            a college where you studied bardic lore and practiced
            your musical magic? Perhaps you were a young runaway
            or orphan, befriended by a wandering bard who became
            your mentor. Or you might have been a spoiled noble
            child tutored by a master. Perhaps you stumbled into the
            clutches of a hag, making a bargain for a musical gift in
            addition to your life and freedom, but at what cost?
        </item>


        <item>
            As you create a cleric, the most important question to
            consider is which deity to serve and what principles you
            want your character to embody. Check with
            your DM to learn which deities are in your campaign.
            Once you’ve chosen a deity, consider your cleric\'s
            relationship to that god. Did you enter this service
            willingly? Or did the god choose you, impelling you into
            service with no regard for your wishes? How do the
            temple priests of your faith regard you: as a champion
            or a troublemaker? What are your ultimate goals? Does
            your deity have a special task in mind for you? Or are
            you striving to prove yourself worthy of a great quest?
        </item>


        <item>
            When making a druid, consider why your character has
            such a close bond with nature. Perhaps your character
            lives in a society where the Old Faith still thrives, or was
            raised by a druid after being abandoned in the depths
            of a forest. Perhaps your character had a dramatic
            encounter with the spirits of nature, coming face to
            face with a giant eagle or dire wolf and surviving the
            experience. Maybe your character was born during an
            epic storm or a volcanic eruption, which was interpreted as a sign that becoming a druid
            was part of your character\'s destiny.

            \n\nHave you always been an adventurer
            as part o f your druidic calling, or did you
            first spend time as a caretaker of a sacred
            grove or spring? Perhaps your homeland was
            befouled by evil, and you took up an adventuring life in
            hopes of finding a new home or purpose.</item>


        <item>
            As you build your fighter, think about two related
            elements of your characters background: Where did
            you get your combat training, and what set you apart
            from the mundane warriors around you? Were you
            particularly ruthless? Did you get extra help from a
            mentor, perhaps because of your exceptional dedication?
            What drove you to this training in the first place? A
            threat to your homeland, a thirst for revenge, or a need
            to prove yourself might all have been factors.

            \n\nYou might have enjoyed formal training in an oble\'s
            army or in a local militia. Perhaps you trained in a war
            academy, learning strategy, tactics, and military history.
            Or you might be self-taught—unpolished but well tested.
            Did you take up the sword as a way to escape the limits
            of life on a farm, or are you following a proud family
            tradition? Where did you acquire your weapons and
            armor? They might have been military issue or family
            heirlooms, or perhaps you scrimped and saved for years
            to buy them. Your armaments are now among your
            most important possessions—the only things that stand
            between you and death\'s embrace.
        </item>


        <item>
            As you make your monk character, think about your
            connection to the monastery where you learned your
            skills and spent your formative years. Were you an
            orphan or a child left on the monastery\'s threshold? Did
            your parents promise you to the monastery in gratitude
            for a service perform ed by the monks? Did you enter
            this secluded life to hide from a crime you committed?
            Or did you choose the monastic life for yourself?

            \n\nConsider why you left. Did the head of your monastery
            choose you for a particularly important mission beyond
            the cloister? Perhaps you were cast out because of
            some violation of the community\'s rules. Did you dread
            leaving, or were you happy to go? Is there something
            you hope to accomplish outside the monastery? Are you
            eager to return to your home?

            \n\nAs a result of the structured life of a monastic
            community and the discipline required to harness ki,
            monks are almost always lawful in alignment.
        </item>


        <item>
            The most important aspect of a paladin character is
        the nature of his or her holy quest. Although the class
        features related to your oath don`t appear until you
        reach 3rd level, plan ahead for that choice by reading
        the oath descriptions at the end of the class. Are you a
        devoted servant of good, loyal to the gods of justice and
        honor, a holy knight in shining armor venturing forth
        to smite evil? Are you a glorious champion of the light,
        cherishing everything beautiful that stands against the
        shadow, a knight whose oath descends from traditions
        older than many of the gods? Or are you an embittered
        loner sworn to take vengeance on those who have done
        great evil, sent as an angel of death by the gods or driven
        by your need for revenge?

        \n\nHow did you experience your call to
        serve as a paladin? Did you hear a whisper
        from an unseen god or angel while you were at
        prayer? Did another paladin sense the potential within
        you and decide to train you as a squire? Or did some
        terrible event—the destruction of your home, perhaps—
        drive you to your quests? Perhaps you stumbled into
        a sacred grove or a hidden elven enclave and found
        yourself called to protect all such refuges of goodness
        and beauty. Or you might have known from your earliest
        memories that the paladin’s life was your calling, almost
        as if you had been sent into the world with that purpose
        stamped on your soul.

        \n\nAs guardians against the forces of wickedness,
        paladins are rarely of any evil alignment. Most of them
        walk the paths of charity and justice. Consider how your
        alignment colors the way you pursue your holy quest
        and the manner in which you con duct yourself before
        gods and mortals. Your oath and alignment might be
        in harmony, or your oath might represent standards of
        behavior that you have not yet attained.
        </item>

        <item>
            As you create your ranger character, consider the nature
            of the training that gave you your particular capabilities.
            Did you train with a single mentor, wandering the wilds
            together until you mastered the ranger’s ways? Did you
            leave your apprenticeship, or was your mentor slain—
            perhaps by the same kind of monster that became your
            favored enemy? Or perhaps you learned your skills as
            part of a band of rangers affiliated with a druidic circle,
            trained in mystic paths as well as wilderness lore. You
            might be self-taught, a recluse who learned combat
            skills, tracking, and even a magical connection to nature
            through the necessity of surviving in the wilds.

            \n\nWhat’s the source of your particular hatred of a
            certain kind of enemy? Did a monster kill someone
            you loved or destroy your home village? Or did you see
            too much of the destruction these monsters cause and
            com mit yourself to reining in their depredations? Is
            your adventuring career a continuation of your work
            in protecting the borderlands, or a significant change?

            \n\nWhat made you join up with a band of adventurers?
            Do you find it challenging to teach new allies the ways
            of the wild, or do you welcome the relief from solitude
            that they offer?
        </item>

        <item>
            As you create your rogue character, consider the
            character’s relationship to the law. Do you have a
            criminal past—or present? Are you on the run from the
            law or from an angry thieves’ guild master? Or did you
            leave your guild in search of bigger risks and bigger
            rewards? Is it greed that drives you in your adventures,
            or some other desire or ideal?

            \n\nWhat was the trigger that led you away from your
            previous life? Did a great con or heist gone terribly
            wrong cause you to reevaluate your career? Maybe
            you were lucky and a successful robbery gave you the
            coin you needed to escape the squalor of your life.
            Did wanderlust finally call you away from your home?
            Perhaps you suddenly found yourself cut off from your
            family or your mentor, and you had to find a new means
            of support. Or maybe you made a new friend—another
            member of your adventuring party — who showed you
            new possibilities for earning a living and employing
            your particular talents.
        </item>

        <item>
            The most important question to consider when creating
            your sorcerer is the origin of your power. As a starting
            character, you will choose an origin that ties to a draconic
            bloodline or the influence of wild magic, but the exact
            source of your power is up to you to decide. Is it a family
            curse, passed down to you from distant ancestors? Or
            did some extraordinary event leave you blessed with
            inherent magic but perhaps scarred as well?

            \n\nHow do you feel about the magical power coursing
            through you? Do you embrace it, try to master it, or
            revel in its unpredictable nature? Is it a blessing or
            a curse? Did you seek it out, or did it find you? Did
            you have the option to refuse it, and do you wish you
            had? What do you intend to do with it? Perhaps you
            feel like you’ve been given this power for some lofty
            purpose. Or you might decide that the power gives you
            the right to do what you want, to take what you want
            from those who lack such power. Perhaps your power
            links you to a powerful individual in the world — the fey
            creature that blessed you at birth, the dragon who put
            a drop of its blood into your veins, the lich who created
            you as an experiment, or the deity who chose you to
            carry this power.
        </item>

        <item>
            As you make your warlock character, spend some time
            thinking about your patron and the obligations that
            your pact imposes upon you. What led you to make the
            pact, and how did you make contact with your patron?
            Were you seduced into summoning a devil, or did you
            seek out the ritual that would allow you to make contact
            with an alien elder god? Did you search for your patron,
            or did your patron find and choose you? Do you chafe
            under the obligations of your pact or serve joyfully in
            anticipation of the rewards promised to you?

            \n\nWork with your DM to determine how big a part your
            pact will play in your character’s adventuring career.
            Your patron’s demands might drive you into adventures,
            or they might consist entirely of small favors you can do
            between adventures.

            \n\nWhat kind of relationship do you have with your
            patron? Is it friendly, antagonistic, uneasy, or romantic?
            How important does your patron consider you to be?
            What part do you play in your patron’s plans? Do you
            know other servants of your patron?

            \n\nHow does your patron communicate with you? If
            you have a familiar, it might occasionally speak with
            your patron’s voice. Some warlocks find messages
            from their patrons etched on trees, mingled among tea
            leaves, or adrift in the clouds — messages that only the
            warlock can see. Other warlocks converse with their
            patrons in dreams or waking visions, or deal only with
            intermediaries.
        </item>

        <item>
            Creating a wizard character demands a backstory
            dominated by at least one extraordinary event. How
            did your character first come into contact with magic?
            How did you discover you had an aptitude for it? Do
            you have a natural talent, or did you simply study
            hard and practice incessantly? Did you encounter a
            magical creature or an ancient tome that taught you the
            basics of magic?

            \n\nWhat drew you forth from your life of study? Did your
            first taste of magical knowledge leave you hungry for
            more? Have you received word of a secret repository
            of knowledge not yet plundered by any other wizard?
            Perhaps you’re simply eager to put your new found
            magical skills to the test in the face of danger.
        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>